Steven H. Scheuer Television History Interviews
Steven H. Scheuer Television History Interviews
1996-1999
Scheuer, Steven H.
39 linear feet (388 audiocassettes, 278 CDs, 110 DVDs, 315 videocassettes, 147 transcripts)
2534133
Biographical History
Steven H. Scheuer (1926- ) is an American film and television historian and critic. He was the editor of the book Movies on TV (originally titled TV Movie Almanac & Ratings) which went through 17 editions between 1958 and 1993. The first guide of its kind (it preceded the still-active Maltin's TV Movies and Video Guide by ten years), the book contained a mixture of movies, videos and TV movies with ratings up to four stars. Scheuer was also the moderator of the syndicated television series, All About TV from 1969 to 1990.
The interviews in this collection were recorded as part of an oral history project conducted through the Center for the Study of Popular Television at Syracuse University in the late 1990s. The project, funded by the Steven H. and Alida Brill Scheuer foundation, accumulated interviews in audio and video formats with key individuals from all parts of the television field. Interviews conducted by Steven Scheuer, David Marc and others include such figures as Ken Burns, Gore Vidal, Joan Ganz Cooney, Av Westin, Howard K. Smith, Dick Clark and many others.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Steven H. Scheuer Television History Interviews consists primarily of audio and video interviews. The collection contains the original audio and video master tapes for each interview, duplicate copies of the audio interviews on audiocassette and compact disc, and duplicate copies of video interviews on VHS, DVD and audiocassette (audio portion only). The collection also contains printed transcripts for most of the interviews and a small amount of research material.
Audio interviews consists of approximately 120 audiotaped interviews (master tapes and duplicates) and Video interviews consists of approximately 65 videotaped interviews (master tapes and duplicates). Some individuals were interviewed on multiple occassions.
Research files contains background information and notes on numerous film and television figures, many of which were eventually interviewed for the project. The files include clippings, photocopies of biographical dictionary entries, printouts from databases, handwritten notes, questions to be asked, and more.
Transcripts comprises typed transcriptions of 147 of the interviews; audio interviews are followed by "(A)" and video interviews are denoted by "(V)." Some transcripts are incomplete; these are indicated in the inventory. Transcripts are in Microsoft Word format. The transcript CDs also include some other files of unidentified type and content.
Digital use copies were created by SU Libraries for the use of researchers, and consist of approximately 400 CDs and DVDs containing digitized versions of most, but not all, of the interviews and transcripts. Audio interviews, on CD, are in .cda format; video interviews are on DVD
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is divided into audio interviews and video interviews. Master tapes and use copies are arranged separately. The five-character alphanumeric catalog number for each interview is given in parenthesis ( ).
Related Material
In addition to the television interviews collection, also holds the
Steven H. Scheuer Papers
, which includes research files, photographs, writings and other material related to Scheuer's professional work as a television critic and historian, as well as the
All About TV Recordings
, a videotape archive of the program moderated by Steven Scheuer from 1969 to 1990. Please refer to for a complete listing of other collections related to television and broadcasting history.
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Popular culture; Scheuer, Steven H.; Television -- United States.; Television actors and actresses -- United States.; Television producers and directors -- United States.; Television journalists -- United States.; Popular culture -- United States.; Audiotapes.; Compact discs.; DVDs.; Interviews.; Videotapes.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Researcher access to the tapes requires advance notice in order to produce a working copy.
Inventory
- Audio interviews, (audiocassettes)
  Digital use copies on CD or DVD are available for interviews marked with an asterisk (*). See Boxes 25-27.
  - Inventory from donor, chart showing number of copies, etc.; not verified (Box 28)
  - Adams, David (A1103), 12/17/96 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Edie (A1102), 5/20/97 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Steve (A1101) *, 9/18/96 (Box 1)
  - Banner, Bob (A1100), 4/3-8/97 (Box 1)
  - Barnouw, Erik (A1099) *, 11/20/96 (Box 1)
  - Beck, Jack (A1098) *, 7/24/97 (Box 1)
  - Block, Richard "Dick" (A1097) *, 3/1/97 (Box 1)
  - Chamberlin, Ward (A1096) *, 11/20/96 (Box 1)
  - Charren, Peggy (A1095) *, 5/5/98 (Box 1)
  - Chaseman, Joel (A1094) *, 6/26/98 (Box 1)
  - Chetwynd, Lionel (A1093) *, 6/5/97; 6/11/97 (Box 1)
  - Clark, Dick (A1092) *, 10/27/98 (Box 1)
  - Cooney, Joan Ganz (A1091) *, 11/21/96 (Box 1)
  - Costello, Robert (A1090) *, 7/15/98 (Box 1)
  - Crichton, Judy (A1089) *, 8/11/98 (Box 1)
  - Dann, Michael (A1088) *, 6/19/96; 7/1/96 (Box 1)
  - Danzig, Jerry (A1087) *, 11/25/97 (Box 1)
  - Day, James (A1086) *, 6/20-21/96 (Box 1)
  - Douglas, Mike (A1085), 10/21/98 (Box 1)
  - Drain, Margaret (A1084) *, 3/1/98 (Box 1)
  - Drew, Robert "Bob" (A1083) *, 12/13/96; 12/27/96 (Box 1)
  - Dunham, Cory (A1106) *, 12/22/98; digital use copies include one CD labelled "self-interview" (Box 1)
  - Dunham, Cory (A1106), (5/27/99) (Box 1)
  - Fanning, David (A1082), 6/1/98 (Box 1)
  - Fates, Gil (A1104), 2/12/99 (Box 1)
  - Felton, Norman (A1081), 5/19/97; 5/30/97 (Box 1)
  - Finkel, Bob (A1080) *, 10/22/96 (Box 1)
  - Fox, Sonny (A1079) *, 4/17/97; 5/1/97 (Box 1)
  - Frank, Reuven (A1078) *, 7/9/96 (Box 1)
  - Fuchs, David (A1077) *, 2/16/98 (Box 1)
  - Glickman, Marty (A1076) *, 10/27/98 (Box 1)
  - Goldenson, Leonard (A1075) *, 10/4/98 (Box 1)
  - Goodman, Julian, 9/16/96; Not in hard copy
  - Grauman, Walter (A1074), 3/6/97 (Box 1)
  - Greaves, William (no number), 7/9/98 (Box 1)
  - Greenbaum, Everet (A1073) *, 11/16/96 (Box 1)
  - Grossman, Lawrence (A1072), 8/27/96 (Box 1)
  - Harris, Susan (no number), 2/10/97 (Box 1)
  - Hartman, David (A1109) *, 7/21/98 (Box 1)
  - Henning, Paul (A1070) *, 9/9/96 (Box 1)
  - Herman, George (A1069) *, 6/25/98 (Box 1)
  - Hickey, Neil (A1068) *, 11/25/97 (Box 1)
  - Iselin, Jay (A1067) *, 1/27/98 (Box 1)
  - Ives, David (A1066) *, 6/2/98 (Box 1)
  - Jankowski, Gene (A1065), 5/18/98 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, John (A1110) *, 7/22/98 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, Lamont (A1064), 9/16/96 (Box 1)
  - Josephson, Marvin (no number), 4/28/98 (Box 1)
  - Justman, Robert (A1062), 11/12/98 (Box 1)
  - Kanter, Hal (no number), 6/26/97 (Box 1)
  - Kitman, Marvin (A1061), 8/9/96 (Box 1)
  - Klugman, Jack (A1060), 12/9-10/96 (Box 1)
  - Kobin, William (A1059), 1/7/97 (Box 1)
  - Konner, Joan (A1105) *, 12/21/98 (Box 1)
  - Kuney, Jack (A1058) *, 5/19/98 (Box 1)
  - Leider, Jerry (Gerald) (A1057) *, 8/22/96 (Box 1)
  - Leiser, Ernie (A1056) *, 5/11/98 (Box 1)
  - Levy, David (A1055) *, 9/17/96 (Box 1)
  - Lewis, Dick (A1054) *, 8/10/98 (Box 1)
  - Link, William (A1053) *, 11/15/96 (Box 1)
  - Lloyd, Norman (A1052) *, undated (Box 1)
  - Loper, Jim (A1051), 1/6/96 (Box 1)
  - Mann, Delbert (A1050) *, 8/23/96 (Box 1)
  - Manning, Gordon (A1049) *, 9/30/97 (Box 1)
  - Mantley, John (A1048), 3/12/97 (Box 1)
  - Marmer, Mike (A1047), 9/26/97 (Box 1)
  - McGhee, Peter (no number), 6/1/98 (Box 1)
  - McMullen, Jay (A1045) *, 11/25/96 (Box 1)
  - McNeely, Jerry (A1044) *, 4/24/97 (Box 1)
  - Mickelson, Sig (A1043) *, 9/6/96 (Box 1)
  - Moore, Dick (A1042), 1/13/9? (Box 1)
  - Morgenthau, Henry (A1041), 5/6/98 (Box 1)
  - Newhart, Bob (A1029) *, 10/14/98 (Box 1)
  - Northshield, Robert "Shad" (A1030) *, 11/12/98 (Box 1)
  - Palmer, Betsy (A1031) *, 4/3/97; 4/11/97 (Box 1)
  - Petrie, Daniel (no number), 2/21/97 (Box 1)
  - Pressman, David (A1032) *, 7/16/98 (Box 1)
  - Richter, Robert (A1033) *, 9/3/98 (Box 1)
  - Rogers, Thomas S. (A1034) *, 3/10/98 (Box 1)
  - Ruben, Albert (A1036) *, 3/9/98 (Box 1)
  - Rubin, Stanley (A1039) *, 3/20/97 (Box 1)
  - Sanders, Marlene (A1037) *, 11/8/96 (Box 1)
  - Schiller, Bob (A1040) *, 1/23/97 (Box 1)
  - Schneider, Al (A1015) *, 2/17/98 (Box 1)
  - Schonfeld, Reese (A1035), 11/5/96 (Box 1)
  - Schonfeld, Reese (A1035) *, 11/15/96 (Box 1)
  - Schwartz, Sherwood (A1006) *, 12/19/96 (Box 1)
  - Schwartzman, Andrew J. (no number), 4/9/98 (Box 1)
  - Segelstein, Irwin (A1023) *, 7/16/98 (Box 1)
  - Sharnik, John (A1038), 12/26/96; 12/30/96 (Box 1)
  - Shaw, David (A1022) *, 9/18/96 (Box 1)
  - Silverstein, Mort (A1026) *, 10/31/96 (Box 1)
  - Simmons, Ed (A1021) *, 5/23/97 (Box 1)
  - Skutch, Ira (A1019) *, 11/13/96 (Box 1)
  - Small, Bill (A1013) *, 12/10/96 (Box 1)
  - Smith, Howard K. (A1014) *, 12/8/97 (Box 1)
  - Socolow, Sanford (A1020) *, 12/18/98 (Box 1)
  - Stanton, Dr. Frank (A1107) *, 5/21/99 (Box 1)
  - Steiger, Rod (A1025) *, 2/13/97 (Box 1)
  - Stewart, Maxine (A1024) *, 10/25/96 (Box 1)
  - Stiller, Jerry (A1111) *, 5/10/99 (Box 1)
  - Stoney, George (A1027) *, 12/17/98 (Box 1)
  - Swift, David (A1108) *, 10/16/96 (Box 1)
  - Talbot, Paul (A1012) *, 11/21/96 (Box 1)
  - Tarloff, Frank (A1011) *, 4/10/97; 4/14/97 (Box 1)
  - Trout, Robert (A1028) *, 3/2/98; 8/21/98 (Box 1)
  - Vancour, Sander (A1005) *, 3/10/98 (Box 1)
  - Wald, Richard (A1018) *, 9/3/98 (Box 1)
  - Wasserman, Al (A1010) *, 12/2/96 (Box 1)
  - Wershba, Joseph (A1009) *, 11/18/96 (Box 1)
  - Westin, Av (A1008) *, 4/29/98 (Box 1)
  - White, Betty (A1007) *, 4/29/97 (Box 1)
  - White, Jack (A1016) *, 9/3/98 (Box 1)
  - White, Jack (A1017) *, 9/11/98 (Box 1)
  - Willis, Jack (A1004) *, 8/17/98 (Box 1)
  - Winant, Ethel (A1003) *, 1/10/97 (Box 1)
  - Witt, Paul Junger (A1000) *, 3/25/97 (Box 1)
  - Wolff, Perry (A1001) *, 12/5/96 (Box 1)
  - Wolper, David (A1002) *, 12/12/96 (Box 1)
  - Audio masters (audiocassettes)
    - A1000-A1090-02 (Box 3)
    - A1091-A1111-02 and misc. duplicates (Box 4)
- Video interviews, (VHS cassettes)
  Digital use copies on DVD are available for interviews marked with an asterisk (*). See Boxes 25-27.
  - Barnouw, Erik *, 10/1/1998 (Box 17)
  - Beck, Jack *, 3/30/1998 (Box 17)
  - Block, Richard "Dick" *, 3/18/1998 (Box 17)
  - Burns, Ken *, 10/2/1998 (Box 17)
  - Chamberlin, Ward *, 12/11/1996 (Box 17)
  - Chaseman, Joel, 11/5/1998 (Box 17)
  - Cooney, Joan Ganz *, 6/11/1998 (Box 17)
  - Dann, Michael *, 7/16/1996 (Box 17)
  - Day, James *, 6/25/1996-6/26/1996 (Box 17)
  - Dorfsman, Lou *, 11/18/1996 (Box 17)
  - Drew, Robert *, 6/8/1998 (Box 17)
  - Finkel, Bob, 12/17/1996 (Box 17)
  - Fox, Sonny *, 3/19/1998 (Box 17)
  - Frank, Reuven *, 9/10/1996 (Box 17)
  - Fuchs, David *, 10/13/1998 (Box 17)
  - Goodman, Julian *, 9/16/1996 (Box 17)
  - Greaves, William *, 10/14/1998 (Box 17)
  - Grossman, Lawrence *, 9/11/1996 (Box 18)
  - Hartman, David *, 10/15/1998 (Box 18)
  - Hickey, Neil *, 10/13/1998 (Box 18)
  - Iselin, Jay, 6/8/1998 (Box 18)
  - Iselin, Jay *, 10/12/1998-10/13/1998 (Box 18)
  - Johnson, Lamont *, 11/25/1996 (Box 18)
  - Kitman, Marvin (Box 18)
  - Leiser, Ernie, 6/10/1998 (Box 18)
  - Leiser, Ernie *, 6/30/1998 (Box 18)
  - Levy, David *, 12/17/1996 (Box 18)
  - Link, William *, 2/4/1997 (Box 18)
  - Lloyd, Norman *, 3/16/1996 (Box 18)
  - Lower, Elmer *, 08/1996 (Box 18)
  - Mann, Abby *, 9/25/1996 (Box 18)
  - Mann, Delbert, 4/23/1996 (Box 18)
  - Mann, Delbert *, 10/2/1996 (Box 18)
  - Manning, Gordon *, 10/24/1997 (Box 18)
  - Manulis, Martin *, 4/26/1996 (Box 19)
  - Markell, Robert *, 1996 (Box 19)
  - Marshall, E.G. *, 10/16/1997 (Box 19)
  - McMullen, Jay *, 6/8/1998 (Box 19)
  - Mickelson, Sig *, 9/27/1996 (Box 19)
  - Moger, Stanley *, 11/25/1996 (Box 19)
  - Moore, Earle K."Dick" *, 11/26/1996 (Box 19)
  - Newman, Edwin *, 11/27/1997 (Box 19)
  - Palmer, Besty, 3/17/1998 (Box 19)
  - Perlmutter, Alvin H. *, 6/9/1998 (Box 19)
  - Pressman, David *, 10/12/1998 (Box 19)
  - Richter, Robert *, 10/14/1998 (Box 19)
  - Rubin, Stanley *, 3/31/1998 (Box 19)
  - Sanders, Marlene *, 1/2/1997 (Box 19)
  - Schaefer, George *, 10/30/1995 (Box 20)
  - Schneider, Alfred *, 6/10/1998 (Box 20)
  - Schonfeld, Reese *, 12/11/1996 (Box 20)
  - Shaw, David, 3/18/1998 (Box 20)
  - Silverstein, Mort *, 11/19/1996 (Box 20)
  - Swift, David, 3/17/1998 (Box 20)
  - Talbot, Paul *, 12/3/1996 (Box 20)
  - Trout, Robert *, 10/12/1998 (Box 20)
  - Vidal, Gore *, 3/8/1996 (Box 20)
  - Wallach, Eli *, 6/29/1998 (Box 20)
  - Wasserman, Al *, 10/17/1997 (Box 20)
  - Weaver, Pat, 1996 (Box 20)
  - Wershba, Joe *, 12/3/1996 (Box 20)
  - Westin, Av *, 7/21/1998 (Box 20)
  - Wolff, Perry "Ski" *, 10/16/1997 (Box 20)
  - Video masters, (BetacamSP, Umatic and miniDV tapes)
    - Beck - Dann (Box 5)
    - Day - Finkel (Box 6)
    - Fox - Grossman (Box 7)
    - Hartman - Levy (Box 8)
    - Levy - Lloyd (Box 9)
    - Lower - Mann (Box 10)
    - Manulis - Markell (Box 11)
    - Manning - Moger (Box 12)
    - Moore - Pressman (Box 13)
    - Rubin - Shaw (Box 14)
    - Shaw - Wasserman (Box 15)
    - Weaver - Wolff (Box 16)
  - Video misc.
    - "Network News in the Age of Cable", Presented by the Center for the Study of Popular TV, 10/25/1997; (Umatic tapes) (Box 13)
    - Audio dubs of video interviews (audio portion only): Barnouw-Wolff, (audiocassettes) (Box 2)
- Research files
  Research files contain a wide range of material on numerous television personalities, including clippings, resumes/work histories, chronologies, filmographies, photocopies of biographical dictionary entries, handwritten notes on questions to be asked, items of correspondence, photocopies of published interviews, and so on. Many, but not all, of the people in the research files were eventually interviewed (see Audio interviews and Video interviews above).
  - A-F (Box 28)
    Persons represented:
    A: Beatrice Arthur
    B: Erik Barnouw, Walter Bernstein, William Blinn, Richard Block, Milton Berle, Shelley Berman, St. Clair Bourne
    C: Peggy Charren, Joel Chaseman, Robert Costello, Richard Crenna
    D: Jerry Danzig, Margaret Drain, Robert Drew
    E: none
    F: Gil Fates (also considerable information on "What's My Line?" and other game shows, at least one of which was hosted by Fates), Norman Felton, Sonny Fox, Bob Finkel, Mark Fowler
  - G-L (Box 28)
    G: Everett Greenbaum, Walter, Grauman, Lawrence Grossman, Leonard H. Goldenson,David Greene
    H: Susan Harris, Paul Henning, Geroge Herman, Neil Hickey, Roy Huggins, Richard Hottelet
    I: none
    J: Gene F. Jankowski, Nicholas Johnson, Marvin Josephson, Robert Justman
    K: Bob Keeshan (Captain Kangaroo), John Kluge, Jack Klugman, Julius (Jack) Kuney
    L: Elmer Lower, Norman Lear, David Levy, James L. Loper, Norman Lloyd
  - M-S (Box 28)
    M: E. G. Marshall, Abby Mann, Delbert Mann, John Mantley, Sig Mickelson, Henry Morgenthau, Harry Morgan, Robert Mulligan, Peter S. McGhee, Jerry McNeely
    N: Bob Newhart, "Network News in the Age of Cable" participant bios
    O: none
    P: Sarah Palfrey, Betsy Palmer, Daniel Petrie
    Q: none
    R: Thomas Rogers, Stanley Rubin
    S: John Schneider, Sherwood Schwartz, Eva Marie Saint, David Shaw
  - T-Z (Box 28)
    T: none
    U: none
    V: Dick Van Dyke
    W: Paul Junger Witt, David Lloyd Wolper
- Transcripts
  With a few exceptions, digital copies of the following transcripts are available on CD in Microsoft Word format (see box 27). Exceptions are noted in the list below.
  - Adams, David (A) (Box 21)
  - Adams, Edie (A) (Box 21)
  - Allen, Steve (A) (Box 21)
  - Banner, Bob (A) (Box 21)
  - Barnouw, Erik (A) (Box 21)
  - Barnouw, Erik (V) (Box 21)
  - Beck, Jack (A) (Box 21)
  - Beck, Jack (V) (Box 21)
  - Block, Richard (A) (Box 21)
  - Block, Richard (V) (Box 21)
  - Bums, Ken (V) (Box 21)
  - Chamberlin, Ward (A) (Box 21)
  - Chamberlin, Ward (V) (Box 21)
  - Charren, Peggy (A) (Box 21)
  - Chaseman, Joel (A) (Box 21)
  - Chaseman, Joel (V) (Box 21)
  - Chetwynd, Lionel (A) (Box 21)
  - Clark, Dick (A) (Box 21)
  - Cooney, Joan Ganz (A) (Box 21)
  - Cooney, Joan Ganz (V) (Box 21)
  - Costello, Robert (A) (Box 21)
  - Crichton, Judy (A) (Box 21)
  - Dann, Michael (A) (Box 21)
  - Dann, Michael (V) (Box 21)
  - Danzig, Jerry (A) (Box 21)
  - Day, James (A) (Box 21)
  - Day, James (V) (Box 21)
  - Dorfsman, Lou (V) (Box 21)
  - Douglas, Mike (A) (Box 21)
  - Drain, Margaret (A) (Box 21)
  - Drew, Robert (A) (Box 21)
  - Drew, Robert (V) (Box 21)
  - Dunham, Cory (A) (Box 21)
  - Fanning, David (A) (Box 21)
  - Fates, Gil (A) (Box 21)
  - Felton, Norman (A) (Box 21)
  - Finkel, Bob (A) (Box 21)
  - Finkel, Bob (V) (Box 21)
  - Fox, Sonny (A) (Box 21)
  - Fox, Sonny (V) (Box 21)
  - Frank, Reuven (A) (Box 22)
  - Frank, Reuven (V) (Box 22)
  - Fuchs, David (A) (Box 22)
  - Fuchs, David (V)
  - Glickman, Marty (A) (Box 22)
  - Goldenson, Leonard (A), incomplete (Box 22)
    Digital format not available.
  - Goodman, Julian (A), incomplete (Box 22)
  - Goodman, Julian (V) (Box 22)
  - Grauman, Walter (A) (Box 22)
  - Greaves, William (A) (Box 22)
  - Greaves, William (V) (Box 22)
  - Greenbaum, Ev (A) (Box 22)
  - Grossman, Lawrence (A) (Box 22)
  - Grossman, Lawrence (V) (Box 22)
  - Hartman, David (A) (Box 22)
  - Hartman, David (V) (Box 22)
  - Henning, Paul/Ruth (A)
  - Herman, George (A) (Box 22)
  - Hickey, Neil (A) (Box 22)
  - Hickey, Neil (V) (Box 22)
  - Iselin, Jay (A) (Box 22)
  - Iselin, Jay (V) (Box 22)
  - Ives, David (A) (Box 22)
  - Jankowski, Gene (A) (Box 22)
  - Johnson, John (A) (Box 22)
  - Johnson, Lamont (A) (Box 22)
  - Johnson, Lamont (V) (Box 22)
  - Justman, Robert (A) (Box 22)
  - Kanter, Hal (A) (Box 22)
  - Kitman, Marvin (A) (Box 22)
  - Kitman, Marvin (V) (Box 22)
  - Klugman, Jack (A) (Box 22)
  - Kobin, Bill (A) (Box 22)
  - Konner, Joan (A) (Box 22)
  - Kuney, Jack (A) (Box 22)
  - Leider, Jerry (A) (Box 22)
  - Leiser, Ernest (A) (Box 22)
  - Leiser, Ernest (V) (Box 22)
  - Levy, David (A) (Box 22)
  - Levy, David (V) (Box 22)
  - Lewis, Richard (A) (Box 22)
  - Link, William (A) (Box 22)
  - Link, William (V) (Box 22)
  - Lloyd, Norman (A) (Box 22)
  - Lloyd, Norman (V) (Box 22)
  - Loper, Jim (A) (Box 22)
  - Lower, Elmer (V) (Box 22)
  - Mann, Abby (V) (Box 23)
  - Mann, Delbert (A) (Box 23)
  - Mann, Delbert (V) (Box 23)
  - Manning, Gordon (A) (Box 23)
  - Manning, Gordon (V) (Box 23)
  - Mantley, John (A) (Box 23)
  - Manulis, Martin (A) (Box 23)
  - Manulis, Martin (V) (Box 23)
  - Markel, Robert (V) (Box 23)
  - Marmer, Mike (A) (Box 23)
  - Marshall, E.G. (V) (Box 23)
  - McGhee, Peter (A) (Box 23)
  - McMullen, Jay (A) (Box 23)
  - McMullen, Jay (V), annotated list does not give location
  - McNeely, Jerry (A) (Box 23)
  - Mickelson, Sig (A) (Box 23)
  - Mickelson, Sig (V) (Box 23)
  - Moger, Stanley (A) (Box 23)
  - Moger, Stanley (V), incomplete (Box 23)
  - Moore, Dick (A) (Box 23)
  - Morgenthau, Henry (A) (Box 23)
  - Newhart, Bob (A) (Box 23)
  - Newman, Edwin (V) (Box 23)
  - Palmer, Betsy (A) (Box 23)
  - Palmer, Betsy (V) (Box 23)
  - Perlmutter, Alvin (V) (Box 23)
  - Petrie, Daniel (A) (Box 23)
  - Pressman, David (A) (Box 23)
  - Pressman, David (V) (Box 23)
  - Richter, Robert (A) (Box 23)
  - Richter, Robert (V) (Box 23)
  - Rogers, Thomas (A) (Box 23)
  - Ruben, Albert (A) (Box 23)
  - Rubin, Stanley (A) (Box 23)
  - Sanders, Marlene (A) (Box 23)
  - Sanders, Marlene (V) (Box 23)
  - Schaefer, George (V) (Box 23)
  - Schiller, Bob (A) (Box 23)
  - Schneider, Al (A) (Box 23)
  - Schneider, Al (V) (Box 23)
  - Schonfeld, Reese (A) (Box 23)
  - Schonfeld, Reese (V) (Box 23)
  - Schwartz, Sherwood (A) (Box 23)
  - Segelstein, Irwin (A) (Box 23)
  - Sharnik, John (A) (Box 23)
  - Shaw, David (A) (Box 24)
  - Shaw, David (V) (Box 24)
  - Silverstein, Mort (A) (Box 24)
  - Silverstein, Mort (V) (Box 24)
  - Simmons, Ed (A) (Box 24)
  - Skutch, Ira (A) (Box 24)
  - Small, Bill (A) (Box 24)
  - Smith, Howard (A) (Box 24)
  - Socolow, Sandy (A) (Box 24)
  - Stanton, Dr. Frank (A) (Box 24)
  - Steiger, Rod (A) (Box 24)
  - Stewart, Maxine (A), incomplete (Box 24)
  - Stiller, Jerry (A) (Box 24)
  - Stoney, George (A) (Box 24)
  - Swift, David (A) (Box 24)
  - Swift, David (V) (Box 24)
  - Talbot, Paul (A) (Box 24)
  - Talbot, Paul (V) (Box 24)
  - Tarloff, Frank (A) (Box 24)
  - Trout, Robert (A) (Box 24)
  - Trout, Robert (V) (Box 24)
  - Vanocur, Sander (A) (Box 24)
  - Vidal, Gore (V) (Box 24)
  - Wald, Richard (A) (Box 24)
  - Wallach, Eli (V) (Box 24)
  - Wasserman, Al (A) (Box 24)
  - Wasserman, Al (V) (Box 24)
  - Weaver, Pat (V), Digital format not available. (Box 24)
  - Wershba, Joseph (A) (Box 24)
  - Wershba, Joe (V) (Box 24)
  - Westin, Av (V) (Box 24)
  - Westin, Av (A) (Box 24)
  - White, Betty (A) (Box 24)
  - White, Jack (A) (Box 24)
  - Willis, Jack (A) (Box 24)
  - Winant, Ethel (A) (Box 24)
  - Witt, Paul Junger (A) (Box 24)
  - Wolff, Perry (A) (Box 24)
  - Wolff, Perry (V) (Box 24)
  - Wolper, David (A) (Box 24)
  - Digital transcripts Adams - Wolper, MS Word files; CDs also include numerous other files of undetermined format; 3 CDs (Box 27)
- Digital use copies, (CD, DVD)
  Digitized use copies created by SU Libraries. Audio are on CD; video are on DVD.
  - Allen - Grossman (Box 25)
  - Hartman - Schiller (Box 26)
  - Schneider - Wolper (Box 27)